http://www.golenders.com/info/privacy-policy.html

Home » Privacy Policy for GoLenders.com
Privacy Policy for GoLenders.comWe at GoLenders.com want to protect the privacy of our visitors.
Sometimes, we may direct you to other websites in order to provide a highly informative browsing experience for you.
GoLenders.com does not store or share your personal information with any third parties.
GoLenders.com May Use Tracking Cookies
GoLenders.com might publish ads which use "cookies" to monitor ad performance. Some advertisers may place and monitor tracking cookies on your browser, or use "beacons" to track the performance of these advertisements.
Cookies are basic tracking codes and are not intended to affect your personal details.
GoLenders.com may use Google Adsense to display and publish ads.
Google Adsense utilizes the "DoubleClick Dart" cookie to track ad performance.
You can find out more about Adsense by browsing : Google's Adsense policies page.
Additionally, you can opt out of having the use of cookies on your browser by visiting: the Cookie Opt-Out service of the Network Advertising initiative.
You can contact us if you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy.
Search By Category
Home Loans
Mortgage Companies
Mortgage Rates
Reverse Mortgage Lenders
Resources
Local Lenders
Apply For Loans
Credit Repair Tips
Mortgage Glossary
Online Mortgage Calculator
What is an FHA Loan?
Apply For Loans
Apply For Loans Category
Mortgage Loans By Region
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
About Us
Contact Us
Listing Change Requests
We are not mortgage brokers or loan companies. The content on this site is for informational purposes only. Use our directory to locate a licensed loan professional in your area for free quotes.
Copyrights 2019 www.golenders.com - All Rights Reserved.
